Guide to the George Ellery Hale Papers HaleGE
California Institute of Technology Archives and Special Collections
- Personal Correspondence and Papers Relating to Individuals, 1865–1950; 1; 20 linear feet (Tape HaleGE_01, Carton 1, Reel 1–40, Carton 3)
  - H. H. Donaldson, 1898–1933; HaleGE_01_00_013_13; 141 pages (Box 13, Folder 13)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 12, frames 219 to 360.
  - M. R. Dongier, 1908–1909; HaleGE_01_00_013_14; 14 pages (Box 13, Folder 14)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 12, frames 361 to 375.
  - A. E. Douglass, 1899–1923; HaleGE_01_00_013_15; 5 pages (Box 13, Folder 15)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 12, frames 376 to 381.
  - Gayton A. Douglass, 1897–1909; HaleGE_01_00_013_16; 7 pages (Box 13, Folder 16)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 12, frames 382 to 389.
  - Mrs. Henry Draper, 1904–1914; HaleGE_01_00_013_17; 30 pages (Box 13, Folder 17)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 12, frames 390 to 420.
  - N. C. Duner, undated; HaleGE_01_00_013_18; 8 pages (Box 13, Folder 18)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 12, frames 421 to 429.
  - Theodore Dunham, Jr., 1931–1933; HaleGE_01_00_014_01; 37 pages (Box 14, Folder 1)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 12, frames 430 to 467.
  - Gano Dunn, 1916–1946; HaleGE_01_00_014_02; 884 pages (Box 14, Folder 2)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 12, frames 468 to 1353.
  - P. L. du Nouy, 1917–1927; HaleGE_01_00_015_01; 11 pages (Box 15, Folder 1)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 13, frames 20 to 31.
  - A. St. C. Dunstan, undated; HaleGE_01_00_015_02; 2 pages (Box 15, Folder 2)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 13, frames 32 to 34.
  - Pierre DuPont, 1916; HaleGE_01_00_015_03; 13 pages (Box 15, Folder 3)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 13, frames 35 to 48.
  - W. F. Durand, 1917–1919; HaleGE_01_00_015_04; 49 pages (Box 15, Folder 4)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 13, frames 49 to 98.
  - M. E. Durkheim, 1916–1917; HaleGE_01_00_015_05; 11 pages (Box 15, Folder 5)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 13, frames 99 to 110.
  - Sir F. W. Dyson, 1901–1935; HaleGE_01_00_015_06; 77 pages (Box 15, Folder 6)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 13, frames 111 to 188.
  - E. M. East, 1917; HaleGE_01_00_015_07; 18 pages (Box 15, Folder 7)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 13, frames 189 to 207.
  - George Eastman, 1927–1933; HaleGE_01_00_015_08; 26 pages (Box 15, Folder 8)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 13, frames 208 to 234.
  - Edward E. Eaton, 1898–1904; HaleGE_01_00_015_09; 74 pages (Box 15, Folder 9)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 13, frames 235 to 309.
  - H. T. Eddy, 1901–1912; HaleGE_01_00_015_10; 12 pages (Box 15, Folder 10)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 13, frames 310 to 322.
  - Graham Edgar, 1918; HaleGE_01_00_015_11; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 11)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 13, frames 323 to 327.
  - Eglise de la Sorbonne, 1912; HaleGE_01_00_015_12; 2 pages (Box 15, Folder 12)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 13, frames 328 to 330.
  - Albert Einstein, 1926–1933; HaleGE_01_00_015_13; 36 pages (Box 15, Folder 13)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 13, frames 331 to 367.
  - Sir John Eliot, 1905; HaleGE_01_00_015_14; 8 pages (Box 15, Folder 14)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 13, frames 368 to 376.
  - Ferdinand Ellerman, 1898–1927; HaleGE_01_00_015_15; 68 pages (Box 15, Folder 15)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 13, frames 377 to 445.
  - Al Ellis, 1928–1933; HaleGE_01_00_015_16; 197 pages (Box 15, Folder 16)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 13, frames 446 to 642.
  - J. W. Ellsworth, 1922–1925; HaleGE_01_00_015_17; 29 pages (Box 15, Folder 17)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 13, frames 643 to 672.
  - Pio Emmanuelli, 1931; HaleGE_01_00_015_18; 10 pages (Box 15, Folder 18)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 13, frames 673 to 683.
  - Paul Epstein, 1913–1934; HaleGE_01_00_015_19; 13 pages (Box 15, Folder 19)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 13, frames 684 to 697.
  - Herbert M. Evans, 1919–1931; HaleGE_01_00_015_20; 12 pages (Box 15, Folder 20)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 13, frames 698 to 710.
  - J. Evershed, 1904–1937; HaleGE_01_00_015_21; 82 pages (Box 15, Folder 21)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 13, frames 711 to 793.
  - Charles Fabry, 1904–1935; HaleGE_01_00_015_22; 28 pages (Box 15, Folder 22)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 13, frames 794 to 822.
  - Faraday Celebrations, 1931; HaleGE_01_00_015_23; 17 pages (Box 15, Folder 23)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 13, frames 823 to 840.
  - S. W. Farnsworth, 1918–1919; HaleGE_01_00_015_24; 7 pages (Box 15, Folder 24)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 13, frames 841 to 848.
  - Beatrix Farrand, 1928–1934; HaleGE_01_00_016_01; 60 pages (Box 16, Folder 1)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 13, frames 849 to 907.
  - Max Farrand, 1926–1936; HaleGE_01_00_016_02; 57 pages (Box 16, Folder 2)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 13, frames 908 to 965.
  - Arthur Farwell, 1928–1932; HaleGE_01_00_016_03; 50 pages (Box 16, Folder 3)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 13, frames 966 to 1016.
  - M. Faye, 1893; HaleGE_01_00_016_04; 2 pages (Box 16, Folder 4)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 13, frames 1017 to 1019.
  - Rev. Julius Fenyi, 1904; HaleGE_01_00_016_05; 6 pages (Box 16, Folder 5)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 13, frames 1020 to 1026.
  - J. C. Fields, 1919–1929; HaleGE_01_00_016_06; 33 pages (Box 16, Folder 6)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 13, frames 1027 to 1060.
  - Finances, 1921–1923; HaleGE_01_00_016_07; 13 pages (Box 16, Folder 7)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 13, frames 1061 to 1074.
  - H. A. Fischer, 1902–1903; HaleGE_01_00_016_08; 7 pages (Box 16, Folder 8)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 13, frames 1075 to 1082.
  - Irving Fisher, 1916; HaleGE_01_00_016_09; 9 pages (Box 16, Folder 9)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 13, frames 1083 to 1092.
  - J. O. Fisher, 1922; HaleGE_01_00_016_10; 7 pages (Box 16, Folder 10)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 13, frames 1093 to 1100.
  - Dr. Martin H. Fischer, 1906–1915; HaleGE_01_00_016_11; 11 pages (Box 16, Folder 11)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 13, frames 1101 to 1113.
  - Arthur H. Fleming, 1908–1935; HaleGE_01_00_016_12; 124 pages (Box 16, Folder 12)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 14, frames 20 to 144.
  - John A. Fleming, 1918–1931; HaleGE_01_00_016_13; 15 pages (Box 16, Folder 13)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 14, frames 145 to 160.
  - Abraham Flexner, 1917–1935; HaleGE_01_00_016_14; 9 pages (Box 16, Folder 14)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 14, frames 161 to 170.
  - Simon Flexner, 1915–1936; HaleGE_01_00_016_15; 245 pages (Box 16, Folder 15)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 14, frames 171 to 416.
  - Alfred D. Flinn, 1918–1932; HaleGE_01_00_016_16; 43 pages (Box 16, Folder 16)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 14, frames 417 to 460.
  - Tod Ford, 1917–1920; HaleGE_01_00_016_17; 38 pages (Box 16, Folder 17)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 14, frames 461 to 499.
  - A. Fowler, 1907–1934; HaleGE_01_00_017_01; 34 pages (Box 17, Folder 1)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 14, frames 500 to 534.
  - Philip Fox, 1905–1935; HaleGE_01_00_017_02; 80 pages (Box 17, Folder 2)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 14, frames 535 to 615.
  - Otto Frank, 1916; HaleGE_01_00_017_03; 2 pages (Box 17, Folder 3)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 14, frames 616 to 618.
  - F. H. Frankland, 1919; HaleGE_01_00_017_04; 2 pages (Box 17, Folder 4)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 14, frames 619 to 621.
  - Maurice Frechet, 1935; HaleGE_01_00_017_05; 9 pages (Box 17, Folder 5)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 14, frames 622 to 631.
  - E. E. Free, 1924–1933; HaleGE_01_00_017_06; 35 pages (Box 17, Folder 6)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 14, frames 632 to 667.
  - John R. Freeman, 1900–1922; HaleGE_01_00_017_07; 17 pages (Box 17, Folder 7)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 14, frames 668 to 685.
  - Robert Freeman, 1912–1927; HaleGE_01_00_017_08; 6 pages (Box 17, Folder 8)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 14, frames 686 to 692.
  - Anna Friedrich, undated; HaleGE_01_00_017_09; 3 pages (Box 17, Folder 9)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 14, frames 693 to 696.
  - E. B. Frost, 1898–1937; HaleGE_01_00_017_10; 427 pages (Box 17, Folder 10–11)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 14, frames 697 to 1125.
  - G. S. Fulcher, 1919–1926; HaleGE_01_00_017_12; 35 pages (Box 17, Folder 12)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 15, frames 20 to 55.
  - Henry Gale, 1907–1932; HaleGE_01_00_017_13; 29 pages (Box 17, Folder 13)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 15, frames 56 to 85.
  - J. R. Garfield, 1918; HaleGE_01_00_017_14; 15 pages (Box 17, Folder 14)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 15, frames 86 to 101.
  - Jack Garrison, 1919–1931; HaleGE_01_00_017_15; 155 pages (Box 17, Folder 15)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 15, frames 102 to 257.
  - F. T. Gates, 1901–1902; HaleGE_01_00_018_01; 2 pages (Box 18, Folder 1)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 15, frames 258 to 260.
  - R. Gautier, 1923; HaleGE_01_00_018_02; 3 pages (Box 18, Folder 2)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 15, frames 261 to 264.
  - Dr. J. Gehring, 1911–1913; HaleGE_01_00_018_03; 7 pages (Box 18, Folder 3)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 15, frames 265 to 272.
  - Sir Archibald Geikie, 1912–1915; HaleGE_01_00_018_04; 18 pages (Box 18, Folder 4)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 15, frames 273 to 291.
  - L. Gianetti, 1916–1938; HaleGE_01_00_018_05; 201 pages (Box 18, Folder 5)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 15, frames 292 to 493.
  - W. S. Gifford, 1917–1929; HaleGE_01_00_018_06; 15 pages (Box 18, Folder 6)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 15, frames 494 to 509.
  - Walter M. Gilbert, 1917–1929; HaleGE_01_00_018_07; 97 pages (Box 18, Folder 7)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 15, frames 510 to 607.
  - D. C. Gilman, 1897–1902; HaleGE_01_00_018_08; 3 pages (Box 18, Folder 8)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 15, frames 608 to 611.
  - G. L. Gilmore, 1915–1930; HaleGE_01_00_018_09; 6 pages (Box 18, Folder 9)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 15, frames 612 to 618.
  - Sir David Gill, 1909–1930; HaleGE_01_00_018_10; 57 pages (Box 18, Folder 10)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 15, frames 619 to 676.
  - Dr. T. H. Gill, 1914; HaleGE_01_00_018_11; 6 pages (Box 18, Folder 11)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 15, frames 677 to 683.
  - Walter J. Gill, Jr., 1903–1904; HaleGE_01_00_018_12; 10 pages (Box 18, Folder 12)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 15, frames 684 to 694.
  - Col. Glassford, 1916–1917; HaleGE_01_00_018_13; 4 pages (Box 18, Folder 13)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 15, frames 695 to 699.
  - Richard Glazebrook, 1932; HaleGE_01_00_018_14; 1 pages (Box 18, Folder 14)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 15, frames 700 to 701.
  - R. H. Goddard, 1918–1919; HaleGE_01_00_018_15; 8 pages (Box 18, Folder 15)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 15, frames 702 to 710.
  - Joel Goldthwait, 1917; HaleGE_01_00_018_16; 7 pages (Box 18, Folder 16)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 15, frames 711 to 718.
  - Bertram and Lydia Goodhue, 1919–1928; HaleGE_01_00_018_17; 206 pages (Box 18, Folder 17)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 15, frames 719 to 924.
  - T. H. Goodspeed, 1935; HaleGE_01_00_018_18; 42 pages (Box 18, Folder 18)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 15, frames 925 to 967.
  - Harry Manley Goodwin, 1907–1936; HaleGE_01_00_018_19; 512 pages (Box 18, Folder 19)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 15, frames 968 to 1480.
  - Harry Manley Goodwin photocopies, 1887–1936; HaleGE_01_00_174_01; 1 boxes (Box 174)
    This box was omitted from filming and digitization.
    Existence and Location of Originals
    This box contains photocopies of approximately 180 letters from Hale to Goodwin. Originals are located in George Ellery Hale Correspondence, mssHM 28397-28553, at the Huntington Library.
  - Samuel Gompers, 1918; HaleGE_01_00_018_20; 2 pages (Box 18, Folder 20)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 15, frames 1481 to 1483.
  - Dr. I. Gottfried, 1919; HaleGE_01_00_018_21; 4 pages (Box 18, Folder 21)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 15, frames 1484 to 1488.
  - Charles W. Gould, 1929; HaleGE_01_00_018_22; 13 pages (Box 18, Folder 22)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 15, frames 1489 to 1498.
  - R. A. Gray, 1932–1933; HaleGE_01_00_019_01; 7 pages (Box 19, Folder 1)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 16, frames 20 to 27.
  - R. A. Gregory, 1917–1936; HaleGE_01_00_019_02; 36 pages (Box 19, Folder 2)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 16, frames 28 to 64.
  - Adm. Robert S. Griffin, 1916–1917; HaleGE_01_00_019_03; 29 pages (Box 19, Folder 3)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 16, frames 65 to 94.
  - C. Guillaume, 1905; HaleGE_01_00_019_04; 4 pages (Box 19, Folder 4)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 16, frames 95 to 99.
  - Marie T. Guizonnier, 1933; HaleGE_01_00_019_05; 8 pages (Box 19, Folder 5)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 16, frames 100 to 108.
  - Sir Robert Hadfield, 1916–1936; HaleGE_01_00_019_06; 121 pages (Box 19, Folder 6)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 16, frames 109 to 230.
  - Arthur T. Hadley, 1919; HaleGE_01_00_019_07; 6 pages (Box 19, Folder 7)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 16, frames 231 to 237.
  - Dr. Arnold Hague, 1902–1914; HaleGE_01_00_019_08; 159 pages (Box 19, Folder 8)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 16, frames 238 to 397.
  - R. Haines, 1915–1916; HaleGE_01_00_019_09; 8 pages (Box 19, Folder 9)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 16, frames 398 to 406.
  - Hale Genealogy, 1934; HaleGE_01_00_019_10; 9 pages (Box 19, Folder 10)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 16, frames 407 to 416.
  - George E. Hale II, 1924–1936; HaleGE_01_00_019_11; 42 pages (Box 19, Folder 11)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 16, frames 417 to 459.
  - George W. Hale, 1897–1919; HaleGE_01_00_019_12; 154 pages (Box 19, Folder 12)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 16, frames 460 to 614.
  - Robert J. Hale, 1916–1920; HaleGE_01_00_019_13; 15 pages (Box 19, Folder 13)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 16, frames 615 to 630.
  - William B. Hale, 1901–1909; HaleGE_01_00_019_14; 228 pages (Box 19, Folder 14)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 16, frames 631 to 854.
  - William B. Hale, 1910–1938; HaleGE_01_00_020_01; 1260 pages (Box 20, Box 21, Folder 1)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 17, frames 20 to 1281.
  - William E. Hale, 1890–1891; HaleGE_01_00_021_02; 39 pages (Box 21, Folder 2)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 18, frames 20 to 59.
  - William E. Hale Fund, 1913–1934; HaleGE_01_00_021_03; 126 pages (Box 21, Folder 3)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 18, frames 60 to 186.
  - William Ellery Hale, 1915–1921; HaleGE_01_00_021_04; 72 pages (Box 21, Folder 4)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 18, frames 187 to 259.
  - Wilfred Hall, 1919; HaleGE_01_00_021_05; 3 pages (Box 21, Folder 5)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 18, frames 260 to 263.
  - J. Halm, 1905; HaleGE_01_00_021_06; 4 pages (Box 21, Folder 6)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 18, frames 264 to 268.
  - William R. Harper, 1897–1905; HaleGE_01_00_021_07; 78 pages (Box 21, Folder 7)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 18, frames 269 to 347.
  - H. W. Harris, 1900–1923; HaleGE_01_00_021_08; 17 pages (Box 21, Folder 8)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 18, frames 348 to 365.
  - Charles C. Harrison, 1916; HaleGE_01_00_021_09; 1 pages (Box 21, Folder 9)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 18, frames 366 to 367.
  - Prof. J. Hartmann, 1904; HaleGE_01_00_021_10; 8 pages (Box 21, Folder 10)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 18, frames 368 to 376.
  - Martha and William W. Harts, 1915–1929; HaleGE_01_00_021_11; 65 pages (Box 21, Folder 11)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 18, frames 377 to 442.
  - B. Hasselberg, 1904; HaleGE_01_00_021_12; 25 pages (Box 21, Folder 12)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 18, frames 443 to 468.
  - Charles H. Hawley, 1903–1906; HaleGE_01_00_021_13; 5 pages (Box 21, Folder 13)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 18, frames 469 to 474.
  - St. John Heiliger, 1925–1927; HaleGE_01_00_021_14; 11 pages (Box 21, Folder 14)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 18, frames 475 to 486.
  - L. J. Henderson, 1918–1937; HaleGE_01_00_021_15; 7 pages (Box 21, Folder 15)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 18, frames 487 to 494.
  - Burton J. Hendrick, 1927–1932; HaleGE_01_00_021_16; 25 pages (Box 21, Folder 16)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 18, frames 495 to 520.
  - Charles H. Herty, 1916; HaleGE_01_00_021_17; 12 pages (Box 21, Folder 17)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 18, frames 521 to 533.
  - Ejnar Hertzsprung, 1912–1914; HaleGE_01_00_021_18; 15 pages (Box 21, Folder 18)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 18, frames 534 to 549.
  - George Higgs and Robert Killip, 1902–1903; HaleGE_01_00_021_19; 20 pages (Box 21, Folder 19)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 18, frames 550 to 570.
  - Charles H. Higgins, 1931–1933; HaleGE_01_00_021_20; 22 pages (Box 21, Folder 20)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 18, frames 571 to 592.
  - Major E. H. Hills, 1913–1917; HaleGE_01_00_021_21; 15 pages (Box 21, Folder 21)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 18, frames 593 to 608.
  - Arthur R. Hinks, 1902–1928; HaleGE_01_00_021_22; 28 pages (Box 21, Folder 22)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 18, frames 609 to 637.
  - Charles F. Holder, 1906–1925; HaleGE_01_00_021_23; 87 pages (Box 21, Folder 23)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 18, frames 638 to 725.
  - Myra C. Hole, 1904–1919; HaleGE_01_00_021_24; 11 pages (Box 21, Folder 24)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 18, frames 726 to 737.
  - W. H. Holmes, 1913–1917; HaleGE_01_00_021_25; 22 pages (Box 21, Folder 25)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 18, frames 738 to 760.
  - Hamilton Holt, 1926–1928; HaleGE_01_00_021_26; 8 pages (Box 21, Folder 26)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 18, frames 761 to 769.
  - John D. Hooker, 1905–1935; HaleGE_01_00_021_27; 110 pages (Box 21, Folder 27)